Guide to the Individual manuscripts, publications, and artifacts, 150 AD. - 2014 MS2135
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Individual manuscripts, typescripts, artifacts, and images, MS2135 Series 1
  - Night on Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington DC, undated; Series 1; Li Fu, Duoruo (Box 35, Folder 2)
    The folder contains serveral copies of a postcard with the title Night on Pennylvania Avenue, Washington DC. This is a reproduction of a watercolor. The artist is Dora Lee. She has also publisehd under the name Duoruo Li Fu. The folder also includes a Washington Post article about Dora Lee (1983 September 1) as well as a brief resume.
  - Shaw urban renewal and model cities program, 1966-1968; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    The following titles were removed from this folder and were cataloged and added to the Special Collections stacks. These are available for use in the Special Collections reading room. Use the library online catalog to retrieve the call no and request the book.
    Shaw School Sites proposals for community discussion Urban renewal plan for the Shaw School Urban Renewal Area project no. 1 Report on public facilities in the Shaw School Urban Renewal Area Role of the District of Columbia in the Urban Renewal Program Workable program 1964-1965 District of Columbia Office of Urban Renewal
    Shaw (Washington, D.C.); Urban renewal
  - Panoramic image of African-American Masons at 7th and Florida NW, Ca. 1920; Series 1 (Oversize-folder 3)
    Description from donor "a panoramic photograph of African-American Masons (or another fraternal organization) posed in their regalia on a street somewhere in Washington around 1920. The photographer is Cosby, 1915 7th St NW, so the location, in front of some brick row houses, may be close to the Cosby studio."
    Gift of Deborah Cooney, 2011 March 8 (2011.018)
  - Robert H. Terrell Law School, Ca. 1930s; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Written on back "named after Robert H. Terrell 1857-1925, DC Munic. Court Judge, offered night law classes at afr. am. from 1931-1950 [1922 13th st., Wash, DC]
    Gift of Deborah Cooney, 2013 June 27 (addition to 2011.018)
  - Emancipation March on Washington button, 1963 August 28; Series 1; This is a white button with black lettering. (Box SHARED Box 17, Item 1)
    Gift of Dorothy Dort Levy, October 25, 2013 (2013.029)
    March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom, Washington, D.C., 1963
  - Art at the home of Donald and Ann Brown, Circa 2014; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    The booklet provides the images, artist name, date, construction material for the art work found in and around the home of GW alums Donald '49,52 and Ann Brown '59. Their home was designed by famous architect Richard Neutra and constructed in 1968.
    The booklet came to Special Collections from Nicole Ferdinando at the GW Buff & Blue Fund. July 14, 2014.
  - Postcards of Washington DC sites, Circa 1950s; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Gift of Colleen McFarland Rademaker on behalf of the Sisters of Charity in Leavenworth KS, 2015 September 15 (2015.050)
    Related Materials
    File contains mid-20th Century postcards depicting buildings and landmarks in Washington DC. collected by Sr. Mary Elizabeth Kelly, SCL (d. 2006)
  - Postcards of Washington DC sites, Circa 1950s; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Orville Miller War Ration Book and ration stamps, Circa 1940; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - More Power to Greater Washington the story of the new Potomac River generating station of the Pepco system, undated; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Civil Defense Evacuation Routes Washington Metropolitan Area, Circa 1940; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Red and green street directory of Washington DC, Arlington Co, and Alexandria Va., 1943; Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Winston Churchill engagement diaries [calendar cards], 1939-1945 (incomplete); Series 1; 1 Linear Feet (Flat box 39)
    Winston Churchill's 30 piece personal engagement diary, dates include 1939-1945 and Winston Churchill's personal handwritten appointment record, July/August 1942
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Digital reproductions of the Engagement Diaries are available electronically at https://archive.org/details/gwulibraries?and%5B%5D=subject%3A%22Churchill%2C+Winston%2C+1874-1965%22&sort=-date
    Gift of the Churchill Center 2015 (2015.048)
  - archeological testing Great Falls Patomack Canal Lock 1, 1979 November; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Analysis and description of the artifacts from block 226 by Paul Y. Inashima, 1980 August 29; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Historical archaeological reconnaissance and assessment Barry's Farm, 1981 April 24; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Archeological investigations on the grounds of the Frederick Douglass Memorial Home, 1981 July; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Report on archeology for Barney Circle, 1981 September 25; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Convention Center site: Washington DC Phase 1 Archeological Survey contract no. 31-2874, 1980 August; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Archaeological testing and data recovery Civic Center site, Washington DC project number 476-1289 [1/2], 1981 October; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Archaeological testing and data recovery Civic Center site, Washington DC project number 476-1289 [2/2], 1981 October; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - A preliminary archeological and historical survey of a portion of Fort Reno Park by Lauana M. Lackey, 1983 June; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Mercy! on the Road to Rosemont by Martha Livdahl Grigg, 2018; Series 1; Grigg, Martha Livdahl, d. 2014; Grigg, William (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Friends of the House of Mercy/Rosement Center was organized by the Episcopal Church. The House of Mercy started in the 1800s as a place to help women who had been prostitutes. The first location was on K street and at some point relocated to the Mt. Pleasant neighborhood. In addition to helping women it also had a nursery and pre-school. This publication documents the founding of the Rosemont Center as an center for early education.
    Friends of the House of Mercy/Rosemont Center -- Washington D.C.
  - Mayor James G. Barrett, Mayor of Washington D.C, 1888; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Radical posters, 1970-1985; Series 1 (Box 41)
    This box contains small to medium size posters (sometimes a centerfold but sometimes simply a colorful image intensive piece. These are not full issues of the publications. These are primarily from short-run radical newspapers in Washington DC. The papers include among others Quicksilver Times, The World Daily, OpenRoad, Crawdaddy, and Washington Free Press. The dates cover 1970-1985 although not every item has dates.
    List of the posters created by staff. When possible a title was provided, but otherwise there is either a description or the words on the posters. Kids have rights! Color them free!; VIII Aniversario Del Asalto Al Moncada Julio 26/53; The Real Story Idi Amin Bilalian News November 26, 1976; May 1st International Workers Day Revolutionary Communist Youth April 1980; Help us commemorate the 75th Anniversary of the Russian Revolution; Liberation Freedom Sisters and Brothers It's Gonna Be A New Morning May 13-27; Remember Malcolm February 21, 1985; When Chairman Mao Gives the Signal We Advance Washington Free Press April; Tet 1968 1972; The victory of the Vietnamese is a victory for us all; El Clarin Programa Borrador del Partido Comunista (ML) April 1977; Miss Yippie 1971; George Jackson quote with figure behind bars - Quicksilver Times September 26-October 11; Smoke In; Yippie festival Insurrection city Smoke-In a gathering of the tribes July 4th Quicksilver Times May 19-29 1970; Welcome KY!; Police Beware No Knock's Gonna Be Hazardous to Your Health; Eldridge Cleaver; Comarde Mao Wants You for the Red Army 1972; Pan Am Announces Holiday Liberation Special: Let Pan Am be your host as you join the people's move to free political prisoners Quicksilver Times September 15-25, 1970; Going to D.C. All Power to the People Rising Up Angry; A message for kids of all ages: why think of going on to college Drop out Quicksilver Times September 15-25 1970; A New Sun Rising; 'A single spark can ignite a prarie fire' Mao image of a person smoking; Reunite Vietnam Quicksilver Times July 3-17 1971; Don't you know you could kill someone with that thing? image of Uncle Sam as a ghost carrying a nuclear bomb; Rally: South African Embassy Black People Must Be Free African Liberation Day 1978; One Class! One Fight Dump Reagan! Daily World 1984 August 30; Read the Young Worker the magazine that speaks for youth! May 1977; People's Bicentennial Commission Leonardo Davinci images; Peole's Bicentennial Commission Thomas Jefferson quote; Prison Poems by Ho Chi Minh Quicksilver Times August 18-28, 1970; Pick a poster choices: Fuck School, Remember Kent State1, Reefer, Riot, and Revolution! Quicksilver Times September 15-25, 1970; Bobby & Ericka are free!!! Quicksilver Times June 2-16, 1971; "Protective reaction*?" Quicksilver Times January 14-27, 1972; Seed Chicago from Vol. 9 No. 2 November 13-31; Would you believe yet another Democratic Convention (the last?) 1972 off our backs May-June 1972; May 1 Quicksilver Times January 16-26, 1971; Fuck Agan*w the all purpose placard Quicksilver Times May 19-29, 1970; Free Bobby Seale! Revolution Quicksilver Times April 5-13, 1970; Reagan II Dump the Destroyer! Daily World July 12, 1984; Workers' Control Dare to Struggle Dare to Win Voice from the Mother Country April 28-May 8; Some pig judge in chicago has discovered that we hold his fascist court in contempt... no shit. Quicksilver Times February 20-March 2, 1970; Mao quote image of tree Quicksilver Times July 31-August 11, 1971; Freddy's 1971 hang up, stoned Dart Board Toy Quicksilver Times December 22, 1970 - January 12, 1971; World-wide May Day events: International Working Class on the March Challenge June 1, 1972; Evict Nixon Quicksilver Times September 11 - 15; TeeVee is a dangerous drug. Smash the habit! Quicksilver Times September 20-October 11; Come to Alderson Free our Sisters off our backs September, 1971; Glory Rich Balagur Crawdaddy; Free Dumbarton Oaks Quicksilver Times June 17-30, 1971; People's Bicentennial Commission July 4, 1974- Honor the Revolution Day; People's Bicentennial Commission The American War is over, but this is far from the case with the American Revolution; Fight for Socialism! Progressive Labor Party Challenge April 7, 1977; OpenRoad Poster#4 Sacco-Vanzetti; The Clash: "Guns of Brixton" Open Road Summer 1982; Defeat Reagan and Reaganism! Vote Daily World October 25, 1984; Dump Reagan Women Demand Peace, Jobs and Equal Rights Daily World March 22, 1984; Reagan's Gotta Go! Dump Reagan Rallies Daily World October 11, 1984; Visit the enchanting island colony of Ireland Quicksilver Times February 15-28, 1972; Break out on May 1st International Workers Day Revolutionary Communist Youth April 1980; Trial by Fire Take Over; May Day and Dawn on the Potomac; Techno-Fascism Quicksilver Times March 24 -April 3, 1970; STP Stop the Pig Serve the People Quicksilver Times May 31-June 21, 1972; quotes from woman refugee from Plain of Jars door September 10-21; Solidarity with African Liberation World Magazine November 10, 1972; Long Lives the Victory of People's War Quicksilver Times April 12-30, 1972; Voice from Mother Country April 28-May 8; The spirit of Fred will never die Rising up Angry; May Day is Jay Day ninth annual Central Park smoke in and parade 1976; Bakunin Centenary 1876-1976 OpenRoad Poster #2
    Gift of Thomas Young, 2019 June 20 (2019.039)
  - Mahaboob Ben Ali and His Chili Bowl: A Story of Family and Identity in the U Street Corridor by Sonali Mirpuri, 2020 May 04; MS2135 Series 1; Mirpuri, Sonali
    Gift of Sonali Mirpuri 2020 May 27 (accession 2020.025)
    Related materials
    MS2285 Ben's Chili Bowl records. The author, Sonali Mirpuri, used these records as part of her research. Finding Aid
  - Washington Light Infantry scrapbook, 1872-1880; MS2135 Series 1 (Box 42, Item 1)
    Gift of the Estate of Josephine R. Shepard November 05, 2020 (accession 2020.027)
    Historical note
    Founded in 1807, the Washington Light Infantry is a military and social organization located in Charleston, South Carolina and still active in the United States. The company was first mustered into active service during the War of 1812, but did not see combat as British troops did not invade South Carolina. In 1836, the company was activated and sent to Florida to combat hostile Seminole Indians during the Seminole Wars. They guarded the city of St. Augustine. Six years later, the company helped establish the South Carolina Military Academy (now The Citadel). During the MexicanAmerican War, the company became part of the Palmetto Regiment and marched into Mexico City in the army of Winfield Scott. When South Carolina seceded from the Union in early 1861, the Washington Light Artillery reformed into three distinct companies and served in the Confederate Army during the American Civil War. In 1916, the unit took the field again, serving as border guards with Mexico near El Paso, Texas, at the request of President Woodrow Wilson. A year later, following the United States' entry into World War I, the WLI served in the United States Army overseas in the 105th Ammunition Train, 55th Field Artillery Brigade, 30th Division. A military banquet is held in Charleston annually on February 22 coincident with Washington's Birthday. [information found the Wikipedia article: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Washington_Light_Infantry]
  - Audio recording Murray Webb Latimer giving a speech, circa 1970-1985; MS2135 Series 1; 1 Cassettes (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Gift of Robert Weisser, 2021 (Accession 2021.015)
    Special Collections has a collection for Murray Webb Latimer
    Latimer, Murray Webb
- Elbridge Colby's "The National Guard of the United States", 1903-1945; MS2135 Series 2; 0.75 Linear feet
  This series contains the manuscript of the book "The National Guard of the United States." A history written by Elbridge Colby.
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter I The recognition of 1903 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 2 The Growth of the Guard to 1912 [1/2] (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 2 The Growth of the Guard to 1912 [2/2] (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 3 The Guard fights for its Life [1/2], undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 3 The Guard fights for its Life [2/2], undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 4 The Border Mobilization of 1916 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 5 The Act of 1916 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 6 World War I, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 7 The Act of 1920 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 8 Building the Modern National Guard [1/2], undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 8 Building the Modern National Guard [2/2], undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 9 The National Guard in World War II, 1941-1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The National Guard of the United States: Chapter 10 Reorganization for New Responsibilities, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Book Arts Specimens, 1600 ca- 1850 ca; MS2135 Series 3; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains title pages from books chiefly in Latin and pictorial works captioned chiefly in English and French. The material dates from 1600-1850, with the bulk of the material dating from 1700-1800. The series includes engraved or wood-blocked title pages, printer's device, and book illustrations. The material was assembled by the donor for study value.
  The material was donated by George Arnstein in 1986.
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Book arts specimens, 1600 ca.-1850 -- --ca. (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Performing Arts Material, 1890-1980; MS2135 Series 4; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains playbills, concert programs, souvenir programs, tickets, and clippings related to various plays, musicals, concerts, ice shows, and other performances in the Washington, D.C. area. The material dates from 1946-1980.
  - Cardozo High School Auditorium--De Paur's Infantry Chorus, 03/06/1951 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Carousel, 09/11/1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Formerly Ephemera Coll no. 17.
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Dancing Waters, 06/1954 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Faith of our Fathers, 06/1963 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheater--Faith of our Fathers, 08/05/1950 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--High Button Shoes, 08/1953 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Madame Butterfly, 08/29/1956 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--The King and I, 08/1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Of Thee I Sing, 06/30/1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre--Phoenix '55, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Constitution Hall--Harry Belafonte "Sing, Man, Sing", 04/24/1956 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Constitution Hall--Fledermaus, 10/20/1951 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Constitution Hall--Anna Russell, 12/07/1958 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Constitution Hall--Anna Rusell, 12/11/1954 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 1950 ca.-1980 -- --ca. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Yearbooks and concert programs for the Friday Morning Music Club. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 10.
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 1972-1982 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Bulletins. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 10.
  - Holiday on Ice of 1955 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Souvenir programs from ice shows held in Washington, D.C. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 20.
  - Ice Capades, 02/1959 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Ice Vogues of 1953 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Lisner Auditorium--Julio and Romiet, 12/05/1947 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Programs from presentations at Lisner Auditorium at George Washington University. Formerly Ephemera Coll no. 18.
  - Lisner Auditorium--Marcel Marceau, 12/29/1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Baptist Church--Leontyne Price, 10/04/1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Theatre--Auntie Mame, 10/1956 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 15
  - National Theatre--Beyond the Fringe, 09/22/1962 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre--Carnival, 03/1961 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre--Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 12/03/1956 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Theatre--Damn Yankees, 02/15/1956 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre--Gentleman Prefer Blondes, 06/02/1952 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Theatre--The Glass Menagerie, 02/06/1947 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Theatre--South Pacific, 07/1954 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Theatre--West Side Story, 09/02/1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - National Theatre--Wonderful Town, 12/1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - New Gayety Theatre various production playbills, 1951 January 29 - 1951 May 21 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Playbills, souvenir programs, tickets, and clippings from presentations at the New Gayety Theatre in Washington, D.C.: Mister Roberts. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 19. Also in this file are two other playbills 1)Death of a Salesman starring Thomas Mitchell, January 29, 1951 and 2) I know My Love starring Lynn Fontanne and Alfred Lund, March 5, 1951.
  - New Gayety Theatre--Fledermaus, 12/1951-01/1952 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Playbills, souvenir programs, tickets, and clippings from presentations at the New Gayety Theatre in Washington, D.C.: Fledermaus. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 19.
  - Olney Theatre, 1949-1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Programs for the Olney Theatre. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 5
  - Paul Robeson Concerts on behalf of United Negro and Allied Veterans of America, 10/16/1947-06/26/1948 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Philadelphia Orchestra, 1946-1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Programs for the Philadelphia Orchestra performing in Washington, D.C. at Constitution Hall. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 7.
  - Princeton Triangle Club--Tour de Farce, 12/16/1961 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Riverside Stadium--Riverside Roller Review, 03/05/1951 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre, 1960-1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Programs for the Shady Grove Music Theatre and Shady Grove Music Fair. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 8.
  - Programs for the Sam S. Shubert Theatre, 1952-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Formerly Ephemera collection no. 6
  - St. James Theatre--The Pajama Game, 08/1954 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1968-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Programs for the Washington Performing Arts Society musical presentations. Formerly Ephemera Coll. no. 9.
  - Benefit performances for Southwest Neighborhood House, 05/16/1963 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    A Solute to Dick Gregory
  - Chicago Civic Opera Company at Washington Auditorium, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Children's Theatre of Washington, 03/28/1953-03/29/1953 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    A production of Hiawatha
  - The Choral Society of Washington, D.C., 04/11/1894 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    The Creation by Haydn
  - Color-Line Entertainment, 08/26/1890 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Production of Westus Pointum Romae
  - Mayflower Cabaret Theatre, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Production Jacques Brel is alive and well and living in paris
  - National Capital Sesquicentennial Freedom Sing, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Singers included Ania Dorfman and Howard Mitchell with the United States Army Band and Chorus
  - National Opera Guild of Washington, D.C. Inc., 04/28/1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Metropolitan Opera productions
  - National Symphony Orchestra, 1963-1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    The Bartered Bride A Comic Opera in Three Acts by Bedrich Smetana and Faust
  - The Gayety Theatre programs, 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre, 1977-1980 -- --ca. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Sweet and Hot The Songs of Harold Arlem, Splendid Rebels by Ernest Joselovitz, and Eddie's Catchy Tunes by Tim Grundmann
  - The Opera Society of Washington, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Phillips Gallery, 1950-1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Song recitals
  - Roadside Washington's Original Barn Theatre, 06/10/1940 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    The Sealed Wall or, What Will Not a Mother Dare? by W.T. Moncrieff
  - Starlight Chamber Music Concert at Meridian Hill Park, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - The Uniquecorn at the Captain's Table, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    promoted as Washington's Long Running Satirical Musical Revue
  - The Washington Civic Opera Association, 01/20/1978-01/21/1978 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    production of Cosi Fan Tutte an Opera in two acts by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart
  - Washington Guitar Society, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Charlie Byrd Classic Guitar Recital
  - Washington Symphony Orchestra, 1912-1913 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Heinrich Hammer conductor
  - Washington Theatre Festival, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Elisabeth Bergner in "Amphitryon 38" and Eddie Dowling in "The Time of Your Life"
  - West End Theatre, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    productions of "Bride of Sirocco", "The Mamet Plays", and "Tom Stoppard's Dirty Linen & New-Found-Land"